http://www.americanlegalfunding.com/privacy-policy

CALL US TODAY AT(866) 954-2321
Privacy Policy////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////ALFMGT NE, LLC
has  established the following policies to protect
your privacy. We suggest you read this notice carefully. We know that the
privacy of personal information is important and we want you to know how we
protect your privacy. We may gather information from you, your attorney or
other third parties in order to evaluate your request for legal funding. That
information may include names, dates of birth, social security number, place of
employment, marital status, medical information, witness statements, police
reports, expert reports, and other documents or information about your pending
legal matter that we deem pertinent to your funding request. To protect your personal information we provide reasonable
security measures designed to prevent unauthorized access to your private
information. We comply with applicable security laws. We refuse to disclose
heath information unless compelled by valid legal process. We maintain control
of your file and information contained therein. We maintain physical,
electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure your personal information is
treated responsibly and in accordance with our privacy policy. We also restrict
access to your personal information within our organization to those employees
who need to know that information to process your transaction, or to conduct ALFMGT
NE, LLC’s business. Employees who have access to customer information may use
it only for legitimate business purposes. We may be required to share your
information with our regular business affiliates for purposes of processing and
completing your application in order to provide you with the service you are
requesting. Our agreements with business affiliates requires them to treat your
personal information in a confidential and secure manner.
